{
    "subject": "Rex_Harrison",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Kay_Kendall",
    "human_readable": "Rex Harrison is married to Kay Kendall.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9883471131324768,
            "question": "Is Kay Kendall married to Rex Harrison?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9736366271972656,
            "question": "When were Rex Harrison and Kay Kendall married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9392637610435486,
            "question": "Are there any children from the marriage of Rex Harrison and Kay Kendall?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.881851315498352,
            "question": "Who is Rex Harrison married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6434296369552612,
            "question": "What is the name of Rex Harrison's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3000379204750061,
            "question": "Who are some famous people that Rex Harrison has worked with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23039332032203674,
            "question": "What was Kay Kendall's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19172286987304688,
            "question": "What was the name of Rex Harrison's most famous role?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1680992990732193,
            "question": "Did Rex Harrison win any awards for his acting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1317649781703949,
            "question": "In what type of movies did Rex Harrison often star?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Rex Harrison is married to Kay Kendall.",
            "html": "yago_1508_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Rex Harrison win any awards for his acting?",
            "html": "yago_1508_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the name of Rex Harrison's most famous role?",
            "html": "yago_1508_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was Kay Kendall's profession?",
            "html": "yago_1508_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_1508_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_1508_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_1508_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_1508_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_1508_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_1508_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_1508_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_1508_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_1508_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_1508_87.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, here is the evaluation of the triple \"Rex Harrison is married to Kay Kendall\":\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThis is because all four documents (1.txt, 77.txt, 24.txt, and 82.txt) mention that Rex Harrison was married to Kay Kendall, specifically in 1957."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Rex Harrison is married to Kay Kendall.\" Specifically, multiple documents mention their marriage:\n- Document 1.txt states, \"Rex Harrison and Kay Kendall were married for 2 years before Kay Kendall died aged 33.\"\n- Document 77.txt mentions, \"Kendall married British actor Rex Harrison in 1957 after they met while filming The Constant Husband in 1955.\" \n- Document 24.txt states, \"Kendall married British actor Rex Harrison in 1957...\"\nThese statements confirm their marriage."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}